Guide to the Early Rice Institute records, 1844-1941 UA 101
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Court cases, 1886-1907 (Boxes 1-50), 241813
  - Subseries B: People of the State of NY vs. Patrick (William Marsh Rice murder trial 1990-1902), 1894-1907 (Boxes 6-40), 241991
    - Testimony (statements, synopses, examinations…) of individuals, 242150
      - Scott, James J., 242172 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Scott, Maria, 242171 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Sheerin, Lillian, 242170 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Short, David L., 242169 (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
      - Speed, Philip, 242168 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Swenson, Eric P., 242167 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Teich, Paul, 242166 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Thompson, Martha E., 242165 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Truesdale, John W., 242164 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Turner, 242163 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Vallely, James F., Detective, 242162 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Van Alstyne, Maria, 242161 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Voss, George H., 242160 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Wallace, John H., 242159 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Westcott, Clarence L., 242158 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Wetherbee, Walter O., 242157 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - White, Charles T., 242156 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - White, Isaac D., 242155 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Whittlesey, John E., 242154 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Willis, Edmund T., 242153 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Woythaler, Albert B., 242152 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Wronkow, H., 242151 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Individuals' corroboration of Jones' testimony, 242147
      - Corroboration of Jones, 242149 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Supplementary memorandum containing references to the corroboration of testimony of Charles F. Jones at preliminary examination, 242148 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Medical testimony, 242123
      - Expert medical opinions, 242146 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Summaries of testimony, 242145 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Summaries and notes, 242144 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Curry, Walker, M.D., 242143 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Donlin, -----, M.D., 242142 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Ewing, James, M.D., 242141 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Flint, Austin, M.D., 242140 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Girdner, John, M.D., 242139 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Hare, Herbert A., M.D., 242138 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Huncke, Max, 242137 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Jones, William L., 242136 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Kemp, R.C., 242135 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Lee, Edward W., M.D., 242134 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Leuf, A.H.P., M.D., 242133 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Loomis, Henry P., M.D., 242132 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Love, Isaac N., M.D., 242131 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - McAllister, John D., 242130 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Millican, Kenneth W., M.D., 242129 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Potter, John S., 242128 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Schultz, Otto H., M.D., 242127 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Thayer, Alfred E., M.D., 242126 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Williams, Hamilton, M.D., 242125 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Witthaus, Rudolph A., M.D., 242124 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Handwriting expert summaries, 242122 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Handwriting experts lists, 242121 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lines of questioning regarding handwriting experts, 242120 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Individuals re. handwriting, 242085
      - Ames, Daniel T., 242119 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Bartlett, Francis, 242118 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Carvalho, David N., 242117 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Clelland, W.W.M., 242116 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Courtney, Frances B., 242115 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Curtis, C.C., 242114 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Davenport, Bennett F., 242113 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Decker, David C., 242112 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Dinsmore, Charles H., 242111 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Drake, W.A., 242110 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Dummer, C.H., 242109 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Ewell, Marshall D., 242108 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Foote, Clarence, 242107 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Frazer, Persifor, 242106 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Gould, H.D., 242105 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Gumpel, M., 242104 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Hagan, William E., 242103 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Harvey, Louis W., 242102 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Hay, Edward B., 242101 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Kinsley, William J., 242100 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Lederle, Ernst J., 242099 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Lewis, A.R., 242098 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Malone, S.G., 242097 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Mann, R. DeWitt, 242096 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Osborn, Albert S., 242095 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Pengelly, W.G., 242094 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Spencer, H.A., 242093 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Tolman, Henry L., 242092 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Truesdale, John, 242091 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tyrrell, John F., 242090 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Vincent, Peter A. Sr., 242089 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Wherry, William M., 242088 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Wood, George W., 242087 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Worth, Frederick, 242086 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 242084 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Memos on handwriting questioning, 242083 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Competency of handwriting experts, 242082 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Trial notes, 242081 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Expert handwriting opinions, 242080 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Handwriting examination results, 242079 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Signature authentication by bank employees, 242078 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Paper companies, 242077 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Thiel Detective Service Company, 242076 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Handwriting evidence: Glass plates, 242067
      - Albums [2] with samples of Rice's handwriting, 242064 (Box 19, Folder -)
      - Documents re. authenticity of signatures, 1881-1906, 242075 (Box 19a, Folder 1)
      - Plates, 1"x4", 242074 (Box 19a, Folder 2)
      - Plates, 3"x8", 242073 (Box 19a, Folder 3-4)
      - Plates, broken, 242072 (Box 19a, Folder 5)
      - Plates, 8"x10", 242071 (Box 19a, Folder 5-6, Box 19b, Folder 7-8)
      - Examples of signatures, on paper, 242070 (Box 19b, Folder 9)
      - Disputed vs. genuine signatures, 242069 (Box 19b, Folder 10)
      - List of sources of glass photo plates, 242068 (Box 19b, Folder 11)
    - Exhibits/evidence, 242057
      - Lists of exhibits, 242066 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Evidence used during trial, 242065 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Cover of will; samples of model lining, 242063 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Berkshire paper buckling marks, 242062 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Berkshire paper weigh sheets, April & July 1900, 242061 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Berkshire typewriter paper buckling marks/tracings, 242060 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Results of search of Louisiana records, 242059 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence regarding evidence for Patrick case, 242058 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Evidence, 242052
      - Photographic copies of Rice's signature, 242056 (Box 21, Folder -)
      - Album: "Photographic exhibits used in the Rice-Patrick Will Case", 242055 (Box 21, Folder -)
      - Various copies of Rice wills, 242054 (Box 21, Folder -)
      - Patrick Folly Illustrated; compiled by American Society of Questioned Document Examiners, 1952, 242053 (Box 21, Folder -)
    - Research, 242031
      - Articles, references, notes, etc. re medical questions, 242051 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Time accounts, 242050 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Formation of the William Marsh Rice Institute, 242049 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - "Some Date Respecting the History of William Marsh Rice and the Formation of Rice Institute," Charles A. Boston, 242048 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Minutes of meeting of W.M. Rice Institute board, 1907, 242047 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Joseph Mayer clerkship, 242046 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Albert T. Patrick background, 242045 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - David L. Short background, 242044 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Morris Meyers background, 242043 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - William Marsh Rice background, 242042 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Compromise of a will, 242041 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - American Manufacturing Co. stock materials, 242040 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - The American Magazine, May 1907, 242039 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - Offprints regarding chloroform, lungs, 242038 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - Reports of Cases Decided in the Court of Appeals of the State of New York with notes, references and index, 1901, 242037 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - Photography and Forgery, July 1901, 242036 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - Admitted and Disputed Writing in the Molineux Case, 1900, 242035 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - In Re Molineux versus a Current Cagliostro, 1901, 242034 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - >A Manual of the Study of Documents, 1894, 242033 (Box 23, Folder -)
      - Medical Record, 1890, 242032 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Trial Notes, 242010
      - Index of witnesses and scheduled interviews, 242030 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Indictments, 242029 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - "Report and recommendation of District Attorney's office upon indictment for forgery, & petitions & notice of motion to discuss indictments", 242028 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence re prosecution of Meyers & Short, June 1908-Jan. 1912, 242027 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Attorneys' arguments, closings, 242026 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Admissibility of a deed, 242025 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Scheme of treatment for admissibility of testimony, 242024 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Impeachment of a witness, 242023 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Refreshing witness' memory, 242022 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Competency of testimony, 242021 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Waiver of the right to refuse to testify, 242020 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Notes re: Patrick and Jones, 242019 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Notes re: examinations and statements, 242018 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Points of law, 242017 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Synopsis of points to be taken; special abstracts, 242016 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - "Chronological view of the facts in respect to the murder of WMR, Vol 3", 242015 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Re: Checks, 242014 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Appeal, 242013 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Request to find with relation to order directing examination of Jones as Witness, with supporting background material, 242012 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Notes, 242011 (Box 25, Folder 7-10)
    - Correspondence, 1900-1902, 242009 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 3 bound volumes of carbons with indices, 242008 (Box 26, Folder -)
    - Appeal: Court of Appeals, State of New York. The People of the State of New York against Albert T. Patrick; Case on Appeal from Court of General Session of the Peace, in and for the County of New York, Vol. I-II, Vol. III-IV, 1902, 242007 (Box 27-28, Folder -)
    - New Trial: …Proceedings on motion for a new trial on ground of newly discovered evidence, 1902, 242006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - New Trial: Papers on motion for a new trial, 242005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings, 241993
      - Scrapbooks (5), 242004 (Box 30, Folder -)
      - Scrapbooks (5), 242003 (Box 31, Folder -)
      - Scrapbooks (4), 242002 (Box 32, Folder -)
      - Scrapbooks (3), including pardon of Patrick, 242001 (Box 33, Folder -)
      - Clips, 1903-1905, 242000 (Box 34, Folder -)
      - Encapsulated clips, Sept. 27-Nov. 1, 1900, 241999 (Box 35, Folder -)
      - Encapsulated clips, Nov. 2, 1900 – April 2, 1901, 241998 (Box 36, Folder -)
      - Encapsulated clips, April 2, 1901 – June 28, 1901, 241997 (Box 37, Folder -)
      - Photocopied clips, Sept. 1900, 241996 (Box 38, Folder -)
      - Photocopied clips, Oct. 1900, 241995 (Box 39, Folder -)
      - Photocopied clips, Nov. 1900, 241994 (Box 40, Folder -)
    - Bound volume of published Briefs, 241992 (Box 115, Folder -)
  - Subseries C: Baldwin vs. Rice, 1886-1908 (Boxes 41-49), 241823
    Adele Baldwin, Julia Roberts, Marian Roberts Robinson, and Lola Morton Seybel, plaintiffs – against – Wm. Marsh Rice Jr., John D. Bartine, and James A. Baker Jr., executors of the Last Will and Testament of William M. Rice, deceased.
    - 1886-1901, 241985
      - Wills of E.B. Rice, 1886, 1892, and 1896, 241990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Answer of Wm. M. Rice re. E.B. Rice will probate, March 1, 1897, 241989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Letters re. Possible familial connections with Wm. M. Rice, 1900-1901, 241988 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Opinion and notes on questions of Texas law, 241987 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Summary in relation to values of location & property, 1901, 241986 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1902, 241978
      - Copy of plaintiff's petition for injunction, Apr. 1902, 241984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Deft.'s exceptions to petition & motion to dissolve order of restraint, Apr. 4, 1902, 241983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Complaint, June 1902, 241982 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Adele Baldwin v. Rice documents, 1902, 241981 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Summons and complaint, 1902, 241980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Petitions of Adele Baldwin in application for letters of admin., with will of E.B. Rice, Oct. 13, 1902, 241979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - 1903, 241947
      - Stipulations, 241977 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Surrogate's Court, Jan. 9, 1903, 241976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Copy complaint, Jan. 1903, 241975 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Summons and complaint, Jan. 20, 1903, 241974 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Notice of appearance, March 10, 1903, 241973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Answer draft, undated, unused, 241972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Draft answer with corrections, 241971 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Answer, April 29, 1903, 241970 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Affidavit of Mark Potter and notice of motion, May 1903, 241969 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Amended answer, May 1903, 241968 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Amended answer "6", May 1903, 241967 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Notice of trial, Notice of motion for preference & affidavit, May 16, 1903, 241966 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Affidavit of Mark W. Potter, May 20, 1903, 241965 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Affidavit of Jared Harrison & notice of motion to strike out, May 24, 1903, 241964 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Order & notice, June 1903, 241963 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston / Motion to strike out, June 6, 1903, 241962 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Affidavit of Mark Potter and notice of motion, June 26, 1903, 241961 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Order and notice, June 26, 1903, 241960 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Reply, July 22, 1903, 241959 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Affidavit of William Harrison & notice of motion, Sept. 8, 1903, 241958 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston & order to show cause, Sept. 10, 1903, 241957 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Motion to strike out parts of reply, Sept. 28, 1903, 241956 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Affidavit of Charles A. Boston, Sept. & Oct. 1903, 241955 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - Order denying motion to strike out reply & Notice of settlement, Oct. 1903, 241954 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Order denying motion to strike out certain portions of reply, Oct. 14, 1903, 241953 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - Proposed order granting commission & Notice of settlement, Nov. 19, 1903, 241952 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Proposed interrogatories, Oct.-Nov., 1903, 241951 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Cross-interrogatories and interrogatories, 1903, 241950 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Cross-interrogatories and interrogatories, Fall 1903, 241949 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Proposed cross-interrogatories, Oct. 1903 – Feb. 1904, 241948 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1904, 241902
      - Stipulations of facts, 1904 (3f), 241946 (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
      - Forms and deeds and legatees, 1904, 241945 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Index of depositions, 241944 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Deposition of O. T. Holt, Jan. 1904, 241943 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Depositions, 1904: Charles Boston, 0. T. Holt, William Rice Jr. (nephew), James A. Baker Jr., Charlotte McKee (sister), Minerva Olds (sister), 241942 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Motion for open commissions, 1904, 241941 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Order granting preference on calendar, Jan. 18, 1904, 241940 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Affidavit of Jared Harrison & Order granting commission, Feb. 3, 1904, 241939 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston & Order granting commission and staying of trial of action, March 4, 1904, 241938 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Deposition of E. P. Turner, March, 1904, 241937 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston & Notice of motion for order permitting descendants to further amend their answer, March 8, 1904, 241936 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston, March 18, 1904, 241935 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Affidavit of Jared Harrison, March 19, 1904, 241934 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Notice containing suggestions by the defendants' counsel of additional parts of depositions, March 24, 1904, 241933 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Notice, March 24, 1904 (unused), 241932 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Notification of adjournment of motion to amend answer, March 25, 1904, 241931 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Affidavit of Charles Boston, March 30, 1904, 241930 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Supplemental memo on part of plaintiffs to oppose motion to amend answer, April 6, 1904, 241929 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Notice of trial, April 12, 1904, 241928 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Proposed order granting motion to amend answer, May 1904, 241927 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Affidavits regarding defendants' motion for re-taxing of costs, May 1904, 241926 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Order grants defendants leave to further amend their answer & Notice of settlement, May 11, 1904, 241925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Notice of service of amendment to amended answer, May 13, 1904, 241924 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Affidavit and order for reargument of motion, May 19, 1904, 241923 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Exhibits related to the testimony of Atty. A.H. Jayne, May 1904, 241922 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Notice to produce, May 24, 1904, 241921 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Subpoena, James A. Baker Jr., May 24, 1904, 241920 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Proposed case on appeal, May 25, 1904, 241919 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - New York Supreme Court Special Term part 5, transcript May 25, 1904, 241918 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Notice to U.S. Fidelity & Guarantee Company, May 31, 1904, 241917 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Order (not used), June 7, 1904, 241916 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Notice of motion to dismiss appeal, June 7, 1904, 241915 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Order & Notice of entry, June 8, 1904, 241914 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - Notice of appeal from order, June 22, 1904, 241913 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - Abandoned pages from 1st proposed decision, July 1904, 241912 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - Notice re. annexed proposed judgment, July 29, 1904, 241911 (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - Bill of costs & Notice of Taxation, Aug. 8, 1904, 241910 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Bill of costs & Notice of Taxation, Aug. 9, 1904, 241909 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - Testimony of James Hussey, Aug. 10, 1904, 241908 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Judgment, Aug. 19, 1904, 241907 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Judgment & Notice of entry, Aug. 19, 1904, 241906 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Order modifying judgment entered Aug. 19, 1904, 241905 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Plaintiffs' exceptions to findings, Aug. 29, 1904, 241904 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Bound volume of published Records and Briefs, 241903 (Box 115, Folder -)
    - 1904 cont. -- Appeal, 241890
      - Papers used in preparation of brief on appeal, n.d., 241901 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Undertaking on appeal, Sept. 1904, 241900 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Notice of appeal, Sept. 6, 1904, 241899 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Affidavit to oppose motion to dismiss appeal or amend appeal book, Oct. 4, 1904, 241898 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Order denying motion to dismiss appeal, Oct. 17, 1904, 241897 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Appellate division opinion, Oct. 1904, 241896 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Notice of argument, Nov. 25 & 29, 1904, 241895 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Opinion, Dec. 1904, 241894 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Suggestions for insertions in draft of case on appeal, n.d., 241893 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Appeal notes, n.d., 241892 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Authorities, precedent, notes at trial, handwritten, 241891 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - 1905, 241876
      - Stipulations, 241889 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Proposed order modifying judgment & Notice of settlement, Jan. 12, 1905, 241888 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Order modifying judgment & Notice of settlement, Jan. 13, 1905, 241887 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Order modifying judgment, Feb. 3, 1905, 241886 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Judgment of affirmance, Feb. 3, 1905, 241885 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Stipulation waving bond, Feb. 9, 1905, 241884 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Notice of appeal, Feb. 9, 1905, 241883 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Affidavit & Notice of motion, Feb. 14, 1905, 241882 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Affidavit & Consent to preference, Feb. 17, 1905, 241881 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Defendant's notice of argument, Feb. 27, 1905, 241880 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Consent that argument of appeal be postponed, Sept. 29, 1905, 241879 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Remittitur, Nov. 22, 1905, 241878 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Notice of motion for reargument and other relief, Dec. 20, 1905, 241877 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - 1906, 241863
      - Stipulations, 241875 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Notes, 241874 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Order on motion for reargument, Feb. 6, 1906 (denied), 241873 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Order on motion for reargument & Notice of entry, Feb. 6, 1906, 241872 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Bill of costs, Feb. 9, 1906, 241871 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Order on remittitur, Feb. 15, 1906, 241870 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Notice of filing remittitur, Feb. 16, 1906, 241869 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Judgment on remittitur, March 6, 1906, 241868 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Summons and complaints, Nov. 21, 1906 (and drafts), 241867 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Complaint, n.d., 241866 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Answer and drafts, Dec. 1906, 241865 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Notice of appearance, Dec. 13, 1906, 241864 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1907, 241835
      - Second action, 241862 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Stipulations, 241861 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Reply, 1907, 241860 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Amended answer, Feb. 1907, 241859 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Affidavit & Notice of Motion for trial by jury of certain specific questions, Feb. 23, 1907, 241858 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Notice of trial, 241857 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Roberts v. Rice memoranda, 241856 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Stipulations, undated, 241855 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Notes, undated, 241854 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Testimony notes, 241853 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Memoranda of Law, Vol. I, 241852 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Memoranda of Law, Vol. II, 241851 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda of Law (Memoranda trial brief), 241850 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda and briefs in Supreme Court, 241849 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda on rights of spouses, 241848 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda on collateral attack of judgment, 241847 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda for defendants in support of motion to strike out matter in the reply, 241846 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - General memoranda by Scott, May 1904, 241845 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - General memoranda, 241844 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda notes, 241843 (Box 47, Folder 4)